indoanime.tv 2015-11-03

# Privacy Policy - indoAnime

This privacy policy sets out how The indo Anime uses and protects any information that you give knowingly or unknowingly to The indo Anime  when you use this website. The indo Anime is committed to your privacy, any information collected is neither sold nor freely given to third parties except where stated in this privacy policy.  
The indo Anime  may, from time to time, change this privacy policy.

As a guest of this website, you should check this page to see if any changes were made. The changes were last made on June 21st, 2015 – Father’s Day.

Information We Directly Collect

*         Optional  
**       Optional, however IP Information may give this detail away on it’s own.  
***     Required, User can avoid giving this information by not signing up for the website.  
****   Automatically Obtained, Can’t be opted out of.

Via the Forum

Time Zone Details**  
Birthday*  
AIM Account*  
MSN Account*  
ICQ Account*  
Yahoo Account*  
Jabber Account*  
Skype Account*  
Personal Website URL*  
Gender*  
Location**  
Interests*  
E-mail***  
IP****

Via the website  
E-mail***  
IP****

IP Address information is automatically obtained anytime the user connects to the website, this cannot be prevented. User profiles can, on request, be deleted. We may require additional validation when a user wishes to delete their profile which will delete all other information that we collect, excluding IP Addresses and information that can be extrapolated from that IP Address.

Requests to delete an account can be e-mailed to admin@indoanime.tv or requested via a message posted on the forums.

Information that is collected by third parties.

The indo Anime uses a chat service called “Chatango”. Their policy is located at this link.  
The indo Anime uses an analytical service called “Google Analytics”, The Google privacy policy is located at this link.  
The indo Anime utilizes advertising services from AdsOptimal, CPMStar, EvolveNation and PlaywireMedia. Click on the name of the advertising service to be directed to their privacy policy.  
The indo Anime utilizes a video player known as JW Player that has analytical services. The video player’s privacy policy is located at this link.  
The indo Anime uses a DNS and DDoS Protection service known as Cloudflare. Here is it’s privacy policy.  
The indo Anime uses a sharing service called AddThis which allows you to share The indo Anime with your friends at the click of a button. Here is it’s privacy policy.  
The indo Anime uses facebook. The embedded widget may indirectly collect information about your activities. Here is the facebook privacy policy.
